Fima Treiger

Full Stack Developer

Ra'anana | 058-700-0568 | fima1fim@hotmail.com Github | LinkedIn | Portfolio

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer experienced in JavaScript based programming, postgreSQL database management and node.js Back-End, focused on Front-End creation of web apps using React and Redux.

Ability to learn new tools and frameworks depending on the companies or clients' needs, with an aptitude for problem-solving issues under pressure, excellent communication skills worker to management, flexible with moment to moment changes on projects, being able to re-focus to complete any task at hand under strict deadlines.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript [ES6+], React, Redux, PostgreSQL, Node.js, Express.js

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Weathytrav - Github | Demo

Full-stack app deployed on Heroku with weatherAPI, database connected to node.js with dotenv and knex

- Uses Bcrypt.js to encrypt user password before inserting into the Database
- PostgreSQL Database created with pgAdmin4 and manipulated with node is and KNEX.js
- Login and Registration forms check the database for existing usernames
- Bcrypt compare used to check encrypted passwords for a match on login

EXPERIENCE

HVAC Technician and Electrician

Central, Israel 03/2019 - 11/2021

Mashav

- Diagnosed and repaired HVAC systems
- Planning and installing HVAC solutions for customers

Reserves NCO Central, Israel **IDF**

08/2017 - 11/2017

- Prepared and installed military radio and communication equipment
- Led and instructed enlisted soldiers

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, JavaScript program

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

12/2021 - 02/2022

Tel-Aviv. Israel

LANGUAGES

Languages (English - fluent, Hebrew - native, Russian - fluent.)